

SKILLS

Data structures and algorithms

Integrated development

environments (IDE)

Databases (SQL-MongoDB)

Postman - Github experience

Software development

PROGRAMMING

Javascript(React.js-Node.js-Express.js)

PHP-Laravel Framework

C# .NET

HTML-CSS

Java-C

Github

github.com/kaanboyacii

Linkedin

linkedin.com/in/kaan-boyaci

Phone

+90 534 523 2689

E-mail

kaanboyacibn@gmail.com

Language

English B2 Turkish Navite

Address

İhsaniye mh. Gökçenefe cd. No:68/1 Tire/İzmir TURKEY

KAAN BOYACI

COMPUTER ENGINEERING STUDENT

ABOUT

I am Kaan, a fourth-year student studying Computer Engineering at Karabuk University. I am always open to learning and improving myself. I have been working on web and cybersecurity, developing projects in these areas.

However, I believe I can work in any field. On the web side, I have projects in front-end (HTML-CSS, JavaScript, React) and back-end (PHP-Laravel, Node.js, Express.js) development. I am knowledgeable and experienced in using shared hosting and Cpanel. I have knowledge of C# .Net and have projects in that area as well. In particular, I have multiple comprehensive projects with Node.js - React.js, which you can check out on my GitHub profile (https://github.com/kaanboyacii).

I have confidence in my projects and myself, and I am constantly improving. Additionally, I have more than five published websites that I have developed as a freelancer. I am currently focused on web development. I'm ready to work remotely.

WORK EXPERIENCE

2020-2021 Store Management (10 months) iz Market / izmir

Invoice entry and exit, invoice system management. Employee management, Project management. Poster

design (Photoshop skill).

2022-2022 Software Developer Intern (1 month) Softtech / Istanbul

Software development, software development processes with the team. Project creation, project management, project presentation. Developments and experiences in web (Node.js, Express.js) and artificial intelligence (Python). Low Code - No Code training. Information Security, Introduction to Scrum framework trainings.

2023-2023 Backend Developer Intern (2 month) Jotform / Ankara

Gaining experience as a backend developer with a focus on PHP and React, collaborating in a team to develop comprehensive projects, primarily centered around scraping. Software, product development, teamwork, web technologies experiences. Creating API services with Node.js, working with APIs, interacting with databases.

EDUCATION

2019-2024 COMPUTER ENGINEERING

(ongoing) Bachelor's Degree / Karabük University

CERTIFICATES

13.12.2021 Certified Ethical Hacker (White Hat) Cyrops (7 Days) (Cyber Homeland)

(eyber Homelana)

14.02.2022 Penetration Testing Certification BG-TEK

(7 Days) (Cyber Homeland)

20.02.2022 Applied Penetration Testing Certification

BTK Academy